bdjobscareers.com 2017-06-06

# BD Jobs Careers Bangladesh | Our Website Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy**

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how we collect, protect and use the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you (“User”, “you” or “your”) provide on the <http://www.bdjobscareers.com/> website and any of its products or services (collectively, “Website” or “Services”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

**Collection of personal information**

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us when you create an account, publish content, fill any online forms on the Website. When required this information may include your email address, name, phone number, address, credit card information, bank information, or other Personal Information. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Website’s features.

**Collection of non-personal information**

When you visit the Website our servers automatically record information that your browser sends. This data may include information such as your computer’s IP address, browser type and version, operating system type and version, language preferences or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and other statistics.

**Use of collected information**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience; improve our website; improve customer service and respond to queries and emails of our customers; send notification emails such as password reminders, updates, etc; run and operate our Website and Services. Non-personal information collected is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding Website traffic and usage. This statistical information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the system.

**Newsletters**

We offer electronic newsletters to which you may voluntarily subscribe at any time. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or by contacting us. However you will continue to receive essential transactional emails.

**Advertisement**

We may display online advertisements and we may share aggregated and non-identifying information about our customers that we collect through the registration process or through online surveys and promotions with certain advertisers. We do not share personally identifiable information about individual customers with advertisers. In some instances, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements to the intended audience.

**Links to other websites**

Our Website contains links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites or third parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that may collect personal information.

**Information security**

We secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of personal information in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and our Website cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party, despite best efforts.

**Changes and amendments**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy relating to the Website or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this privacy policy on the Website. When we do we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. Continued use of the Website after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.

**Acceptance of this policy**

You acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Website or its Services you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to use or access the Website and its Services.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

**BD Jobs Careers**

Mohammad Pur, Humayon Road

Dhaka -1215, Bangladesh

Contact us through Email
